onepieceofbleach.com 2016-04-25

# AB 1513 Sucks - Privacy Policy

Information Collection, Use, and Sharing 

We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone. 

We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request. 

Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about changes to the site. 

Your Access to and Control Over Information 

You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us at [contact@1513.sucks](mailto:contact@1513.sucks). 

Security 

We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline. 

If we collect sensitive information, that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. You can verify this by looking for a closed lock icon or looking for "https" at the beginning of the address of the web page. 

Cookies 

We use "cookies" on this site. A cookie is a piece of data stored on a site visitor's hard drive to help us improve your access to our site and identify repeat visitors to our site. For instance, when we use a cookie to identify you, you would not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our site. Cookies can also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information on our site. 

Surveys 

From time-to-time our site requests information via surveys. Participation in these surveys is completely voluntary and you may choose whether or not to participate and therefore disclose this information. Information requested may include contact information, and demographic information. 

Links 

This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of any other site that collects personally identifiable information. 

Updates 

Our Privacy Policy may change from time to time and all updates will be posted on this page.
